<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hello from Rachna</title>
    <link>https://rachnasrivastava.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hello from Rachna</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2023 Rachna Srivastava</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rachnasrivastava.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://rachnasrivastava.com/blog/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rachnasrivastava.com/blog/welcome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article explains how to install the theme and provides example files.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freedom</title>
      <link>https://rachnasrivastava.com/stories/freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 01:31:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rachnasrivastava.com/stories/freedom/</guid>
      <description>Freedom The backyard was full of beautiful flowers, their fragrance was spreading all around. Yellow, red, blue and purple various colour butterflies were hovering on them. This view was joyful for heart and eyes. Everyone in family liked it ,but Johnny was happiest. He had great fascination for butterflies.
One evening, Johnny was out in garden and looking at flowers. Then,He saw a yellow butterfly and kept chasing till he caught it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am Big Toe!</title>
      <link>https://rachnasrivastava.com/stories/toe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 01:31:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rachnasrivastava.com/stories/toe/</guid>
      <description>I am Big Toe! Ever since God created human, Big toes considered itself superior to other toes. They always treated them rudely and scornfully. Other toes did not like this. But they did not care much about it and were happy themselves.Because they knew that a co-ordination of all toes is helping human to walk.
One day Big toes got an opportunity to show off and Right Big Toe started “I think We hold a very high value, without us human can’t walk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rainbow</title>
      <link>https://rachnasrivastava.com/stories/rainbow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 01:31:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rachnasrivastava.com/stories/rainbow/</guid>
      <description>Rainbow God created nature and filled it with beautiful colours. The beautiful green of trees was immensely re-freshing, while the sky was soothing blue. And the beautiful and vibrant red of flowers was filling hearts with joy and energy. Everything looked wonderful with colours.
The world was at its best with colours; but some other problem was brewing in. Every colour considered itself most important. Red said “I am the most joyful and vibrant, so I am most important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandma&#39;s Glasses</title>
      <link>https://rachnasrivastava.com/stories/grandmasglasses/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 01:31:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rachnasrivastava.com/stories/grandmasglasses/</guid>
      <description>Grandma&amp;rsquo;s Glasses Grandma entered the room; and said “Charlie dear, have you seen my glasses? I forgot where have i left them. Can you please help me searching?”
Charlie who was busy playing Lego in his room, did not bother to look up also; said “Grandma, I am busy playing, Can you please ask mother to help you. She must be knowing where are your glasses.”
Grandma replied “She is not at home dear, she has gone out for some work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hanna and Panna</title>
      <link>https://rachnasrivastava.com/stories/hannaandpanna/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 01:31:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rachnasrivastava.com/stories/hannaandpanna/</guid>
      <description>Hanna and Panna Hanna and Panna were two cows, who stayed in the neighborhood. Hanna was shiny white skinned whereas Panna had a patchy rough brown skin. A beautiful skin made Hanna very proud of its looks and he looked-down Panna. They used to roam and graze together but could never become good friends because of Hanna’s haughtiness.
It was beautiful Spring all around. Trees were laden with shiny new leaves and pastures were filled with lush green grass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Rachna</title>
      <link>https://rachnasrivastava.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rachnasrivastava.com/about/</guid>
      <description>About Rachna    Photo of Rachna  Rachna Srivastava is an author of children’s books. She strives to convey everyday morals and sensitivities in young minds. Her stories use simple characters and sometimes animals as characters to allow children to imbibe the values from the stories easily.
She stays in Waterloo,Ontario with her husband and three-year-old son. Her son is source of inspiration of her writing. She enjoys watching cartoons movies, reading and writing children’s books, and travelling to new places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Calligraphy</title>
      <link>https://rachnasrivastava.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rachnasrivastava.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Social Media:
Facebook
Twitter
Email:
  Submit Reset  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
